vakilsearch.com 2013-03-24

# VakilSearch

### PRIVACY POLICY

Vakilsearch created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to yourprivacy and the protection of your information. As part of the normal operation of services, wecollect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy weprovide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about theway your information is collected and used.

OVERVIEW

We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriateprotection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information")you share with us.

Personal information means information about you that is personally identifiable including, butnot limited to, your name, address, email address or other contact information.

Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access toinformation, which is publicly available on our Site. However, in order to provide you withcertain services given under the Site, you must create an account (“Account”) and provide uswith your email address and password that you will use for your Account (“Requested Details”).We may request additional Personal Information in the future.

We use Personal Information for the following purposes: to identify and authenticate your accessto Design Connect’s services that you are authorized to access, to provide you with the servicesprovided under the Site, to improve our services to you and to contact you.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Our site's Booking Form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, address,telephone number and email address), and demographic information (like your zip code/pincode).

Certain information, such as your name, e-mail addresses, is collected in order to, among otherthings, verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.

We also may obtain and collect information about you when you log into our Site through thirdparty social networking websites. Users may log into our Site using their log in credentials fromvarious third party social network websites, which may change from time to time, including,without limitation, Facebook, Google and Twitter. When you get into our Site, in accordancewith the particular third party’s log in process, you will be directed to enter your user ID (oftenyour email) and your password. We store the information that we receive from you through thesesocial networking sites along with other information that we collect or receive from you. Forinformation about how Facebook, Google and Twitter may disclose your information, includingany information that you make public, please consult the applicable site’s privacy policy. We donot have any control over how any of these sites uses or discloses the personal information thatyou provide to them.

If you sign into our service through Facebook, after entering your email address and Facebookpassword, we might request your permission to access and/or access information that you haveshared and made public on these websites. For information about how these websites maydisclose your information, please consult their Privacy Policy. We have no control over howthese websites uses or discloses the personal information that you provide to it. We store theinformation that we receive from these websites along with other information that we collectfrom you or receive about you.

In the future, if you decide to avail any services we offer, then we will need to collect certainfinancial information, such as your credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billingaddress (" **Financial Information** "). Financial Information that is collected is used to check yourqualifications for registration, to bill you for products and services, and for other purposes. Wedo not share Financial Information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provideyou with the service.

COOKIES

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our Websites. "Cookies"are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We alsooffer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also helpus provide information, which is targeted to your interests.

EXTERNAL LINKS ON WEBSITE

The Offering may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources. Vakilsearch mayhave no control over any websites or resources, which are provided by companies or personsother than Design Connect.

You acknowledge and agree that Vakilsearch is not responsible for the availability of any suchexternal sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products or other materials onor available from such websites or resources.

You acknowledge and agree that Vakilsearch is not liable for any loss or damage which may beincurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a resultof any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising,products or other materials on, or available from, such websites or resources.

OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use customer contact information from the booking form to send you information aboutDesign Connect. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer ourWebsite. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographicinformation. Finally, we may use your IP address to help protect our partners and ourselves fromfraud. Vakilsearch will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomesavailable.

CONFIDENTIALITY

You further acknowledge that the Offering may contain information which is designatedconfidential by Vakilsearch and that you shall not disclose such information without DesignConnect’s prior written consent.

Your information is regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any thirdparty, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities.

We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mailaddress for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by us will only be in connection with the provisionof agreed services and products.

Vakilsearch.com makes every effort to maintain the confidentiality of any information submittedby you to our System. Vakilsearch avails the services of a number of lawyers/advocates/CAs/CSs/tax consultants etc. However, because Vakilsearch.com cannot control the conduct ofothers and cannot be held liable for their actions. Do not make any confessions or admissions.Vakilsearch.com is not responsible for the release or improper use of such information by anysuch person whose services we avail or any release due to error or failure in the System.

OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your privatecommunications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in waysnot otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting andforegoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcementagencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully interceptor access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse yourinformation that they collect from our Websites. Therefore, although we use industry standardpractices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that yourpersonally identifiable information or private communications would always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about youto any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personallyidentifiable information may be disclosed.

**_Advertiser:_** We aggregate (gather up data across all our members' accounts) personallyidentifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable mannerto advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However,in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used toidentify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, creditcard number and bank account number, are never disclosed to marketing advertisers. We mayuse third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employcookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertisingeffectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags iscompletely anonymous.

**_For Payment:_** We may use and share the User information with reliable and reputed third-partypayment gateway to whom we are associated in order to ensure swift and comfortable paymentmechanism for the User. The third-party payment gateway and other payment transactionprocessors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required toprovide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommendthat you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personalinformation and your credit/debit card details will be handled by these providers. Once you leaveour store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longergoverned by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

**_External Service Providers:_** There may be a number of services offered by external serviceproviders that help you use our Websites. If you choose to use these optional services, and inthe course of doing so, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant thempermission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed bytheir private policy.

**_Other Corporate Entities:_** We share much of our data, including personally identifiableinformation about you, with our parent and/or subsidiaries that are committed to serving youronline needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities haveaccess to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat informationthey obtain from their other members. It is possible that We and/or its subsidiaries, or anycombination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should sucha combination occur, you should expect that we would share some or all of your information inorder to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent itoccurs).

**_Law and Order:_** We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third partiesto enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and youauthorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other governmentofficials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with aninvestigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or mayexpose us or you to legal liability.

YOUR USE OF OTHER MEMBERS INFORMATION

As a user of the Service you might have access to other users' personal information. You agreeto use this information solely for sharing and communicating on the site. The Company and itsusers shall not tolerate spam of any kind. Accounts suspected of causing spam will be deletedimmediately and such users shall not be allowed to register again. You are thus not permitted tocontact any user of the Service via e-mail, marketing messages or other kinds of spam withoutreceiving their prior consent. Please feel free to report any users you suspect of using the Serviceas a platform for spamming by contacting customer support.

You understand that all information (such as data files, written text, computer software, orimages) which you may have access to as part of, or through your use of, the Offering are thesole responsibility of the person from which such content originated.

ACCESSING, REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PROFILE

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted duringregistration. If you change any information we may keep track of your old information. You canchange your registration information such as: name, address, city, state, zip code, country, phonenumber, and profile.

To remove your profile so that others cannot view it, contact our customer support team.We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain circumstances,such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further,such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical andlegal constraints, including stored 'back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that allof your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases inresponse to your requests.

TRADEMARK, COPYRIGHT, AND PATENT SUBMITTED MATERIAL

As part of an order for certain trademark, copyright, and patent products, you may be required tosubmit to Vakilsearch materials – such as specimens, drawings, or copies of your work – in orderfor it to complete your order and submit your document(s) to the relevant government office.You understand that Vakilsearch does not share these materials with any third party except whennecessary to complete your order. Furthermore, you understand that while it may retain digitalcopies of your submission, Vakilsearch does not retain physical copies of your submissions andwill not return those materials to you. All physical materials that Vakilsearch does not submit togovernment offices as part of your application will be securely destroyed.

CONTROL OF YOUR PASSWORD

When you sign up to become a Member, you will also be asked to choose a password. You areentirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. You agree not to usethe account, username, email address or password of another Member at any time or to discloseyour password to any third party. If you choose to share this information with third partiesto provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your logininformation and password and therefore should review each third party's privacy policy.

You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password, includingfees. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personallyidentifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf.Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediatelychange your password. You agree to notify us immediately if you suspect any consistentunauthorized use of your account or access to your password even after changing it.

OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addressesthe use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose yourinformation to other parties, whether they are on our Websites or on other sites throughout theInternet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose tothem. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies.Since we do not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questionsbefore you disclose your personal information to others.

SECURITY

We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employmany different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by membersinside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. Youtherefore agree that any security breaches beyond the control of our standard security proceduresare at your sole risk and discretion.

NOTIFICATION OF MODIFICATIONS AND CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce yourrights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changeswill be minor. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes aresignificant, we will provide a more prominent notice at the homepage, and other places we deemappropriate so our users are always aware of the changes.
